Register of the Frank McAdams Albrecht Papers, 1928-1965
Hoover Institution Archives
Frank McAdams Albrecht Papers,
1928-1965
68013
Albrecht, Frank McAdams, 1901-
8 manuscript boxes (3.2 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Orders, reports, correspondence, and drafts of speeches, relating to U.S. military engineering in the European Theater during World War II and in the U.S. in the interwar period.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1968.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Access Points
United States. Army. Corps of Engineers.; United States. Army--Officers.; Military engineering.; World War, 1939-1945.; World War, 1939-1945--Engineering and construction.; United States--Armed Forces.
Biographical Note
1901, June 11 Born, Denver, Colorado
1923 B.S., U.S. Military Academy, West Point, New York
1926 Degree in Civil Engineering, Cornell University, Ithaca, New York
1926 Married Page Williams of San Antonio, Texas
1939 The Command and General Staff School, Fort Leavenworth, Kansas, Regular Course
1942 Colonel
1942 Staff Officer to the Chief Engineer's Office of the Services of Supply in the European Theater of Operations in England. Later Deputy Chief Engineer for Planning
1943 Senior U.S. Logistical Officer on the early Joint-Combined Staff, which became General Eisenhower's Supreme Headquarters. He was the logistics member of a team that presented the original Overlord Plan for the Allied Invasion
1943 Chief of Staff of the Forward Echelon of the Communications Zone
1944 At the U.S. element of the Allied Control of Germany. Responsible for planning for the demobilization of the German Army under Allied control and other demilitarization measures
1945 Engineer of the Fourth Army
1953 Brigadier General
1953-1955 Chief Engineer, U.S. Army, Europe
1955 In Charge of logistics for Exercise SAGEBRUSH. Director of Plans and Programs in the Office of the Deputy Chief of Staff for Logistics of the Army General Staff in Washington, D.C.
1957 Major General
1959 Division Engineer for the Corps of Engineers in the Southeast United States, Bermuda, Puerto Rico, and Panama
Scope and Content of Collection
Orders, reports, correspondence, and drafts of speeches, relating to U.S. military engineering in the European Theater during World War II and in the U.S. in the interwar period.
Container List
- Biographical File, 1928-1960. (Box No. 1-2.)
  Biographical data, recommendations for promotion, commendations, a portrait (8x10 black/white print), and 201 Military Personnel file.
  - 201 Military Personnel File (Box 1.)
    - 1943-1945
      - General
      - Travel
      - Leave
      - Awards and commendations
      - Miscellaneous
      - Rosters
      - Honors and mementos
      - Reports and articles
    - 1946-1949
      - Officer's and Warrant Officer's qualification card copy
      - Miscellaneous
      - General orders
      - Travel
      - Leave
      - Society of American Military Engineers
      - Fellowship, U.S. - British
      - Speeches
      - Pay and allowance
      - Commendations
    - 1950-1951
      - Household goods
      - Leave
      - Miscellaneous
      - Officers
      - Pay and allowance
      - Publicity
      - Purchases
      - Quarters
      - Special orders
      - Travel
    - 1952-1953
      - Leave
      - Miscellaneous
      - Officers
      - Publicity
      - Purchases
      - Quarters
      - Pay and allowance
      - Special orders
      - Travel
    - 1954-1956 (Box 2.)
      - Household goods
      - Leave
      - Medical
      - Miscellaneous
      - Officer
      - Publicity
      - Purchases
      - Quarters
      - Pay and allowances
      - Special orders
      - Travel
    - 1957
      - Household goods
      - Leave
      - Medical
      - Miscellaneous
      - Officer
      - Publicity
      - Purchases
      - Quarters
      - Pay and allowances
      - Special orders
    - 1958
      - Household goods
      - Leave
      - Medical
      - Miscellaneous
      - Officer
      - Pay and allowances
      - Publicity
      - Purchases
      - Quarters
      - Special orders
      - Travel
    - 1959
      - Household goods
      - Leave
      - Medical
      - Miscellaneous
      - Publicity
      - Purchases
      - Pay and allowances
      - Officer
      - Special orders
    - 1960
      - Household goods
      - Leave
      - Medical
      - Miscellaneous
      - Officer
      - Pay and allowances
      - Publicity
      - Purchases
      - Quarters
      - Special orders
      - Travel
- Correspondence, 1943-1945. (Box No. 3-8.)
  Arranged alphabetically by name of correspondent.
  - Unidentified, 1944-1956 (Box 3.)
  - A. G. Gilbert Company (New Haven, Connecticut), 1948
  - Aandahl, Fred G. (Washington, D.C.), 1951-1953
  - Abbey, Colonel Richard S. (Washington, D. C.), 1957
  - Ackerman, Captain J. O. (Omaha, Nebraska), 1943-1960
  - Adams, Brigadier General A. J. (Washington, D.C.), 1957
  - Adams, F. R. (New York), 1960
  - Ahnfeld, Colonel A. L. (Langley Air Base, Virginia), 1956
  - Aiken, I. M. (Brunswick, Georgia), 1960
  - Alexieff, Major General T. S. (HQ. U.S. Group C.C. APO 742 U.S. Army), 1945
  - Allen, Brigadier General I. L. (Washington, D.C.), 1956-1957
  - Allen, Lieutenant Colonel Raymond, 1955, 1957
  - American Express, Inc., 1953
  - American Corporation (New York, New York), 1940
  - Andersson, Colonel K. S. (Fort Belvoir, Virginia), 1953
  - Army & Navy Publishing Co. Inc., (Baton Rouge, Virginia), 1942
  - Arnold, B. (West Palm Beach, Florida), 1958-1959
  - Arva Motor Hotel (Arlington, Virginia), 1959
  - Associated General Contractors of America, Inc., 1947, 1960
  - Associated Military Stores, Inc., (Chicago, Illinois), 1946
  - Atlanta Freight Bureau (Atlanta, Georgia), 1960
  - Back, Major General George I. (Washington, D.C.), 1953
  - Bacon, Agnes (Tryon, North Carolina), 1958
  - Baker, Commander J. O. (Atlanta, Georgia), 1957
  - Baker, Brigadier General William G., Jr., (Washington, D.C.), 1954-1955
  - Ballard, Colonel R. J. (HQ., 7th Army), 1953
  - Baltzer, Colonel Nyles W. (New Britain, Connecticut), 1957
  - Barber, Major Homer C. (n.d.)
  - Barker, Major General Ray W. (Manlius, New York), 1948-1958
  - Barnes, Colonel Elmer (Washington, D.C.), 1950
  - Barnes, Kenneth (Tulsa, Oklahoma), 1948
  - Barnes, Colonel Lynn C. (New York, New York), 1958
  - Barney, Brigadier General Keith R. (Washington, D.C.), 1955-1960
  - Barrett, O. Slack (Cincinnati, Ohio), 1950
  - Barth, Brigadier General Charles H., Jr., 1943
  - Bartlett, Colonel William H., 1953
  - Barton, Colonel Ray M., 1953
  - Baudouine, Major Tex G. (Bismarck, North Dakota), 1950
  - Beach, Major General Dwight E. (Washington, D.C.), 1957
  - Beard, Colonel William N. (Fort Rucker, Alabama), 1958
  - Beck, Gertrude A. L. (Tryon, North Carolina), 1945
  - Beecher, Brigadier General Frederick (London, England), 1945
  - Bell, Burton J. (Atlanta, Georgia), 1958
  - Bendetsen, Colonel Karl, 1945, 1952
  - Beninato, A. J. and Sons (Williamsburg, Virginia), 1956
  - Bennett, Lieutenant General Gerald W. (Langley Air Force Base, Virginia), 1955
  - Berg, Oscar N. (Minot, North Dakota), 1958
  - Berrigan, Colonel Paul D. (San Francisco, California), 1955
  - Bertsch, Major L. (Bremerhaven, Germany), 1953
  - Binns, Major General John J. (San Francisco, California), 1955, 1957
  - Bisbort, Colonel Harold E. (New York, New York), 1959-1960
  - Black, Colonel Arthur H. (Oakland, California), 1957
  - Blitch, Iris F. (Washington, D.C.), 1959
  - Blore, Lieutenant Colonel Richard E., 1954
  - Blumenfeld, Lieutenant Colonel Charles H., 1944
  - Boerne Chamber of Commerce (Boerne, Texas), 1946
  - Bogart, Brigadier General T. F. (Fort Stewart, Georgia), 1960
  - Boiler, Major William F. (West Point, New York), 1958
  - Booth, Major General Donald P. (Washington, D.C.), 1955
  - Bork, Bridagier General Lester S., 1955, 1960
  - Bosley, Captain R. M., 1953, 1955
  - Bostock, George M. (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), 1949
  - Bottcher, Ira (Deer River, Minnesota), 1950
  - Bowen, Colonel James E., Jr. Washington, D.C.), 1948
  - Bower, Colonel William N. (Marietta, Georgia), 1960
  - Bowman, Brigadier General Frank O. (Fort Belvoir, Virginia), 1951
  - Bowman, James C. (Southport, North Carolina), 1958
  - Boyce, Lieutenant Colonel W. Craig, Jr., 1957, 1960
  - Briachon, Jean (Loiret, France), 1953-1954
  - Brier, Major John K. (Fort George G. Meade, Maryland), 1957
  - British Travel Association (New York, New York), 1958
  - Broadfoot, William G., Jr. (Wilmington, North Caroline), 1958-1959
  - Brooks, Colonel Irvin W. (New York, New York), 1958
  - Brown, Colonel Desloge (St. Paul, Minnesota), 1960
  - Brown, Brigadier General Edward A., Jr., 1942, 1955, 1958
  - Brown, Colonel Harry E. (Raleigh, North Carolina), 1959
  - Brown, Norman (Tampa, Florida), 1958-1959
  - Brown, Colonel Roland C. (Wilmington, North Carolina), 1953
  - Browning, Major General Samuel R. (Durham, North Carolina), 1959
  - Brownjohn, General Sir Nevel, 1943-1960
  - Brunschwig, Colonel Roger, 1945
  - Brunsdale, Governor Norman (Bismarck, North Dakota), 1951-1953
  - Brunson, Colonel M. V. (San Antonio, Texas), 1947
  - Buckle, Major General Denys, 1950, 1958
  - Buckman, H. H. (Washington, D.C.), 1960
  - Burke, Colonel Paul (Bowling Green, Virginia), 1957
  - Burres, Lieutenant General Withers, 1952-1953
  - Camblor, William (New York, New York), 1957
  - Cameron, Colonel Ralph H. (San Antonio, Texas), 1948
  - Campbell, Lieutenant Colonel Williams E., Jr. (Atlanta, Georgia), 1958
  - Canan, Colonel Howard V. (Washington, D.C.), 1946, 1953
  - Cannon, Lieutenant Colonel Craig (Jacksonville, Florida), 1957
  - Carey, Colonel Walter C. (New Orleans, Louisiana), 1958
  - Carlson, Colonel G. W. (Washigton, D.C.), 1958
  - Carney, Billie (Mrs. Leroy P.), 1954
  - Carter, Mayor Lee (Hartwell, Georgia), 1959
  - Carter, Brigadier General William A., Jr., 1953-1960
  - Cary, Colonel Victor L. (Langley Air Force Base, Virginia), 1955
  - Cassidy, Brigadier General William F. (San Francisco, California), 1958
  - Chapman, G. H. (Minneapolis, Minnesota), 1950
  - Chapman, Howard W. (Atlanta, Georgia), 1960
  - Cheever, Colonel Charles E. (San Antonio, Texas), 1953, 1957
  - Chorpening, Major General C. H., 1949, 1954
  - Clark, Colonel Allen F., Jr. (Portland, Oregon), 1959
  - Clarke, Lieutenant Colonel Daniel (New York, New York), 1955
  - Clein, Gertrude (Washington, D.C.), 1957
  - Clemente and Company (Washington, D.C.), 1951-1953
  - Clendenen, Colonel Clarence C. (Stanford, California), 1965
  - Click, David (Clewiston, Florida), 1957-1959
  - Colglazier, Major General Robert W. (Washington, D.C.), 1959
  - Collier, Lieutenant General J. H. (Fort Sam Houston, Texas), 1957
  - Conn, William V. (Atlanta, Georgia), 1960
  - Conner, John L. (Atlanta, Georgia), 1958-1960
  - Conner, Master Sergeant Rex E. (Fort Sam Houston, Texas), 1950
  - Cookingham, L. P., 1959
  - Coosa-Alabama River Improvement Association, Inc. (Montgomery, Alabama), 1960
  - Copeland, Mayor M. A. (Brunswick, Georgia), 1960
  - Copp, Lieutenant Colonel Fulton W., 1947, 1952
  - Cornell, E. A. (Tulsa, Oklahoma), 1946
  - Coslow, George R. (Miami Beach, Florida), 1958
  - Coulter, Major General John B., 1947, 1950
  - Cove, Lieutenant Colonel Joseph E., 1956
  - Cox, Sergeant Vivian (New York, New York), 1946
  - Crawford, Brigadier General Joseph D. (London, England), 1958
  - Crawford, Major General R. W. (Memphis, Tennessee), 1950
  - Critz, J. Ben (Dallas, Texas), 1949
  - Crumley, Commodore R. M. (Atlanta, Georgia), 1959
  - Culhane, Lieutenant Colonel R. J. Washington, D.C.), 1955
  - Culpepper, Caughey B. (Atlanta, Georgia), 1958, 1960
  - Cummings, Major General Emerson L. (Washington, D.C.), 1955
  - Cunningham, Frederick A. (Foxholme, North Dakota), 1950
  - Dail, G. E., Jr. (Atlanta, Georgia), 1960
  - Darneau (?) (Olivet - Loiret, France), 1952
  - Dart, Harry C. (Eustis, Florida), 1955, 1959
  - Davidson, Alfred H., Jr., 1946-1957
  - Davies, Hal S. (Minot, North Dakota), 1951
  - Day, Major General Francis M. (New York, New York), 1956-1957
  - Dean, Colonel Reginald L., 1950, 1954 (Box 4.)
  - Delchamps, A. F. (Mobile, Alabasma), 1960
  - De Naeyer, Rob (Brussels, Belgium), 1958
  - Denit, Major General Guy B., 1953
  - DeNoya, Lieutenant Colonel Louis L., 1953
  - Devers, Lieutenant General Jacob L., 1943-1944
  - Dewey, George S. (Goldsboro, North Carolina), 1958
  - Diercks, Colonel Frederick O. (Washington, D.C.), 1957
  - Dines, Dines and Holme (Denver, Colorado), 1955
  - Dobes, William L. (Atlanta, Georgia), 1958
  - Dole, Captain R. W. (Cocoa Beach, Florida), 1960
  - Draughon, Colonel Robert W. (Port Arthur, Texas), 1948
  - DuBose, Major Marion (Athens, Georgia), 1946
  - Dudley, Colonel John H. (New York, New York), 1955
  - Easterbrook, Major General Ernest F. (Fort Rucker, Alabama), 1959-1960
  - Eastman, Lieutenant Colonel H. C., 1944
  - Eddleman, General Clyde D. (New York, New York), 1959
  - Eddy, Lieutenant General Manton C., 1953, 1957
  - Edwards, J. L. (Hampton, Virginia), 1955
  - Edwards, Robert C. (Clemson, South Carolina), 1959
  - Edwards, Colonel Sheffield (Arlington, Virginia), 1958
  - Elliott, Carl (Washington, D.C.), 1960
  - Emery, Colonel Frank, 1946
  - Emight, Colonel Harry M. (Camp Gordon, Georgia), 1954
  - Engel, William P. (Birmingham, Alabama), 1959
  - Espy, Lieutenant Colonel B. W. (Langley Air Force Base, Virginia), 1955
  - Evans, Major General Ira K. (Fort Lee, Virginia), 1957
  - Evans, James A. (Birmingham, Alabama), 1957, 1960
  - Falkner Colonel F. H. (Washington, D.C.), 1955
  - Farley, Captain Charles A. (San Francisco, California), 1947
  - Farquhar, James T., 1950
  - Farrell, Colonel Carl Y. (Fort Sam Houston, Texas), 1957, 1959
  - Fellowship of U.S.-British Comrades (Washington, D.C.), 1947
  - Fickinger, Paul L. (Billings, Montana), 1951
  - Ficklen, Holmes (San Antonio, Texas), 1948
  - Fielden, Major General R. G., 1945
  - Finch, Colonel J. R. G. (Washington, D.C.), 1960
  - Fischer, Colonel Harry O. (Chicago, Illinois), 1959
  - Fleming, Colonel R. J. (Washington, D.C.), 1950
  - Fles, Barthold (Dallas, Texas), 1946
  - Flint River Valley Development Association (Albany, Georgia), 1960
  - Florida State Board of Engineer Examiners, Office of the Board (Gainesville, Florida), 1960
  - Foglesong, 1st Lieutenant Jimmy L., 1955
  - Fonger, Lieutenant Colonel R. E. (New York, New York), 1949
  - Forney, Colonel Frank H. (Washington, D.C.), 1948
  - Fort, Dudley C. (Atlanta, Georgia), 1960
  - Fort McPherson Officers' Open Mess (Fort McPherson, Georgia), 1960
  - Fort Meyer Officers' Open Mess (Fort Meyer, Virginia), 1956, 1959
  - Fort Meyer Post Hospital Commanding Officer (Arlington Virginia), 1958
  - Foster, J. E. (Greenville, South Carolina), 1955
  - Foster, Colonel Kenneth W. (Washington, D.C.), 1955-1956
  - Fox, John (Wilmington, North Carolina), 1958
  - Franey, Colonel James M., 1944, 1959
  - Frawley, Major Thomas F., 1944
  - Freystedt (Heidelberg, Germany), 1954
  - Fry, Major General James C. (Washington, D.C.), 1955-1956
  - Fuller, Lieutenant Colonel Cecil H., 1953-1959
  - Fuller, Maynard G. (Fort Sam Houston, Texas), 1950
  - Gage, Brigadier General Phil S. (Atlanta, Georgia), 1960
  - Gailey, Major General C. K., 1953
  - Galloway, Major General G. E. (Fort Belvoir Virginia), 1954, 1960
  - Galloway, Lieutenant Colonel James V., n.d.
  - Ganoe, Colonel W. A., 1944
  - Gard, Major General R. G. (Langley Air Force Base, Virginia), 1955
  - Garforth, Colonel W., 1943, 1945
  - Gazin, Major General Maurice J. (Paris, France), 1958, 1960
  - Gee, Colonel Herbert C. (West Palm Beach, Florida), 1958-1960
  - Georgetown University, Registrar (Washington, D.C.), 1956
  - Georgia Chamber of Commerce (Atlanta, Georgia), 1960
  - Gilchrist, Lieutenant Colonel Frank (Russellville, Arkansas), 1949
  - Gillem, Lieutenant General Alvan C. (Atlanta, Georgia), 1950
  - Gitton, J. (Orleans, France), 1952
  - Gleboff, Captain Nicolas V. (New York, New York), 1946
  - Goulding, Molly (Los Angeles, California), 1955
  - Gold, Jack (Richmond, Virginia), 1956
  - Goldstein Brothers (Hampton, Virginia), 1955
  - Good, Lieutenant Colonel Dean K., 1958
  - Grandell, Colonel Riel S. (Fort Leavenworth, Kansas), 1956
  - Grant, Edward (San Francisco, California), 1946-1948
  - Grider, Colonel Edgar L., 1958-1960
  - Griffin, Governor Marvin (Atlanta, Georgia), 1957
  - Griffith, Dennis E. (Fort Sam Houston, Texas), 1950
  - Grimond, Henri, 1952
  - Gullatt, Doswell (Washington, D.C.), 1960
  - Haas, George (Mobile, Alabama), 1959
  - Hall, Wilton (Anderson, South Carolina), 1959
  - Hallock, Colonel Duncan, 1958-1960
  - Hammond, James H. (Columbia, South Carolina), 1960
  - Hammond, Ralph (Arab, Alabama), 1960
  - Handy, General Thomas T. (Fort George G. Meade, Maryland), 1950-1953
  - Hanmer, Brigadier General Steven R. (Washington, D.C.), 1956-1960
  - Hannis, Colonel Henry F. (Washington, D.C.), 1950
  - Hansen, Major Ray S. (New York, New York), 1960
  - Hanson, Colonel George W., 1945
  - Hardin, Brigadier General John R. (Washington, D.C.), 1953
  - Harding, Colonel Chester K., 1954, 1957
  - Harper, T. Harley (Rome, Georgia), 1960
  - Harris, R. Reader (Pall Mall, S.W.1, England), 1943
  - Harrison, Brigadier General D. (Ripon, Yorks, England), 1943
  - Harton, Colonel Thomas G. (Atlanta, Georgia), 1960
  - Hartsfield, William B. (Atlanta, Georgia), 1960
  - Harvey, Colonel Raymond J., 1954
  - Hasje, Coleman L. (Lubbock, Texas), 1948
  - Hastings, Major General K. L. (Washington, D.C.), 1957
  - Hatch, A. C., 1956
  - Hausauer, Major General Karl F., 1946-1960
  - Hayes, Colonel William P. (Albuquerque, New Mexico), 1948
  - Hays, Robert H. (Buffalo, New York), 1958
  - Heard, Shaefer, 1958-1960
  - Hearthside (Tryon, North Carolina), 1956
  - Heath, Major General Louis T. (Sandia Base, New Mexico), 1957
  - Heiman, Brigadier General David W. (Washington, D.C.), 1957
  - Henning, Brigadier General William H. (London, England), 1958
  - Hertford, Major General Kenner F., 1948-1959
  - Hicks, Colonel William, 1953-1956
  - Hill, Lister (Montgomery, Alabama), 1959
  - Hille, Colonel Henry L. (Riverdale, North Dakota), 1955-1956
  - Hillman, Lieutenant Colonel Robert G., 1953
  - Hitt, W. H. (West Palm Beach, Florida), 1953
  - Hjelle, John O. (Bismarck, North Dakota), 1953
  - Hodes, Lieutenant General Henry I., 1949-1956
  - Hodges, Luther H. (Raleigh, North Carolina), 1957
  - Hoffman, Brigadier General Hugh (Fort Sam Houston, Texas), 1950
  - Hoge, Lieutenant General W. M., 1953-1954
  - Holcombe, Lieutenant General J. H. (Fort Benning, Georgia), 1960
  - Holland, Brigadier General Jeremiah P. (Langley Air Force Base, Virginia), 1955
  - Holle, Major General Charles G., 1953-1960 (Box 5.)
  - Holtzworth, Brigadier General B. A. (Fort Monroe, Virginia), 1955
  - Hood, Colonel John R. (Washington, D.C.), 1958
  - Hoover Company (North Canton, Ohio), 1955
  - Hopkins, Lieutenant Colonel C. E., 1944
  - Horn, Colonel Russell E. (York, Pennsylvania), 1950-1960
  - Horning, Dean F. (Dallas, Texas), 1958
  - Housemen, Major General Evan H. (Brooklyn, New York), 1958
  - Houston, George B. (Fort Sam Houston, Texas), 1950
  - Houston, Commodore Sam E., Jr. (Atlanta, Georgia), 1957
  - Howard, W. B. (New Orleans, Louisiana), 1949
  - Howardd, Eugene, Jr. (Saphire, North Carolina), 1960
  - Howell, Lieutenant Colonel Leon (New York, New York), 1959
  - Hutchings, Brigadier General Henry, Jr., 1946-1955
  - Illinois State Bonus Service Recognition Board (Springfield, Illinois), 1947
  - Ingils, Major General, 1943
  - Itschner, Lieutenant General Emerson C. (Washington, D.C.), 1953-1960
  - Jacoby, Colonel A. M., 1957-1960
  - Jefferies, R. M. (Moncks, Corner, South Carolina), 1960
  - Jewett, Brigadier General Richard L., 1959
  - Johns Hopkins University (Baltimore, Maryland), 1956
  - Johns, Brigadier General Dwight F., 1944-1957
  - Johnson, Major General D. J., 1955-1956
  - Johnson, Major General Douglas V., 1957-1958
  - Johnson, Major General Max S. (Carlisle Barracks, Pennsylvania), 1957
  - Johnson, P. McK. (Phoebus, Virginia), 1956
  - Johnson, Brigadier General W. M. (Missoula, Montana), 1958
  - Jones, Henry (Bismarck, North Dakota), 1954
  - Jones, Major General Herbert M. (Washington, D.C.), 1957
  - Jones, Stewart E. (Washington, D.C.), 1957
  - Kehm, Colonel Harold D. (Arlington, Virginia), 1958-1960
  - Kellogg, Captain William W. (Highlands, Texas), 1948
  - Kent, Colonel James R., 1958
  - Ker, Major General Howard, 1955-1958
  - Kerkering, Colonel John H. (Fort Belvoir, Virginia), 1960
  - Kerr, Colonel Maurice, 1944, 1946
  - Kessinger, Colonel H. E., 1945
  - Kilday, Paul J. (Washington, D.C.), 1948
  - King, J. Edward (Chicago, Illinois), 1957
  - Klein, Major General John A. (Langley Air Force Base, Virginia), 1955
  - Klemp, Colonel Hugh E. (Langley Air Force Base, Virginia), 1956
  - Knowland, Senator William F. (Washington, D.C.), 1945
  - Kohlos, Colonel F. Henry, 1951-1958
  - Kowalski, Lieutenant Colonel Frank, Jr., 1944
  - Kuldell, Brigadier General R. C. (Houston, Texas), 1948
  - LaFlamme, Master Sergeant Vincent J. (Seattle, Washington), 1956
  - Lamar, Lieutenant Colonel R. J. (Washington, D.C.), 1947
  - Lane, Patricia (Paris, France), 1954
  - Laney, Lieutenant R. David, 1955, 1958
  - Langley, Lieutenant Colonel William C. (Tullahoma, Tennessee), 1960
  - Lanier, P. W., 1950-1951
  - Lauben, Colonel Phillip S. (Governors Island, New York), 1948
  - Laurion, Lieutenant Colonel Larry E. (Fort Leavenworth, Kansas), 1948
  - Lauterstein, Lewis (San Antonio, Texas), 1947
  - Lawrence, C. E. (Mrs.) (Leesville, Louisiana), 1955
  - Lawton, D. B. (Rome, Georgia), 1960
  - Leaf, Emily (Mrs. William N.), (Washington, D.C.), 1948-1959
  - Leaf, Harriet W. (Akron, Ohio), 1959
  - Leaf, Colonel William N., 1946-1948
  - Leckie, Lieutenant Colonel William E.
  - Leduc, Francois (Paris, France), 1953-1954
  - Lee, Lieutenant Commander, H., Jr., USN, 1951
  - Lee, Lieutenant General John C. H., 1944, 1957
  - Lemley, Colonel Harry J., Jr. (New York, New York), 1960
  - Leone, L. P. (Berlin, Germany), 1952
  - Le Tourneau, R. G., Inc. (Longview, Texas), 1947
  - Lieber, Brigadier General Albert C. (Washington, D.C.), 1953
  - Lindsey, John A., Jr. (Fort Sam Houston, Texas), 1950
  - Lipham, Captain C. L. (Atlanta, Georgia), 1960
  - Lipscomb, Brigadier General Thomas H., 1958
  - LOEWE OPTA Aktiegesellschaft (Kronach, Germany), 1956
  - Loiseau, Maitre Jacques (Loury, Loiret, France), 1952-1954
  - Lord, Brigadier General Royal B., 1942-1949
  - Luplow, Colonel W. D. (Washington, D.C.), 1948
  - McCarty, Brian K. (West Palm Beach, Florida), 1960
  - McClurkin, L. C. (Savannah, Georgia), 1960
  - McCowan, M. Ryan (Tryon, North Carolina), 1956
  - McCreary, Mrs. William H. (Fort Belvoir, Virginia), 1956
  - McDonough, Jack J. (Atlanta, Georgia), 1959
  - McElwee, Lieutenant Colonel Frank D. (San Juan, Puerto Rico), 1957